import React from 'react';
import Ink from 'react-ink';


const riddles = [{
    question: 'What has four fingers and a thumb, but is not living?',
    answer: 'glove'
}, {
    question: 'I have keys but no locks. I have a space but no room. You can enter, but can\'t go outside. What am I?',
    answer: 'keyboard'
}, {
    question: 'I can only live where there is light, but I die if the light shines on me. What am I?',
    answer: 'shadow'
}, {
    question: 'What flies when it’s born, lies when it’s alive, and runs when it’s dead?',
    answer: 'snow flake'
}, {
    question: 'What gets wet when drying?',
    answer: 'towel'
}, {
    question: 'Every night I’m told what to do, and each morning I do what I’m told. But I still don’t escape your scold. What i am?',
    answer: 'alarm'
}, {
    question: 'Give me food, and I will live. Give me water, and I will die. What Am I?',
    answer: 'fire'
}, {
    question: 'What comes once in a minute, twice in a moment, but never in a thousand years?',
    answer: 'm'
}, {
    question: 'I am a mother and a father but have never given birth. I’m rarely still, but I never wander. What am I?',
    answer: 'tree'
}, {
    question: 'Hurt without moving. Poison without touching. Bear the truth and the lies. Are not to be judged by our size. What are we?',
    answer: 'words'
}, {
    question: 'Which word in the dictionary is spelled incorrectly?',
    answer: 'incorrectly'
}, {
    question: 'I’m always there, some distance away. Somewhere between land or sea and sky I lay. You may move towards me, yet distant I stay. What am I?',
    answer: 'horizon'
}];


class Error extends React.Component {

    constructor(props) {
        super(props);

        console.log(props);

        this.state = {
            riddle: riddles[Math.floor(Math.random() * riddles.length)],
            answered: false,
            correct: false,
        };
    }

    _checkRiddle() {
        this.setState({answered: true});

        if (this.refs.answer.value === this.state.riddle.answer) {
            this.setState({correct: true});
            console.log('righ');
        } else {
            this.setState({correct: false});
            console.log('wrong');
        }
    }

    render() {
        return (
            <div className="error">
                <header><h3>Internal server error</h3></header>
                {this.props.noRiddle && <p>Something went wrong. Our best engineers are working to fix the issue.</p>}
                {!this.props.noRiddle && <div>
                    <p>Something went wrong. Our best engineers are working to fix the issue. In the meantime, here's a
                       riddle for you :</p>
                    <p className="riddle">{this.state.riddle.question}</p>
                    <div className="flex align-center margin-left-8px">
                        <input type="text" ref="answer"/>
                        <button onClick={this._checkRiddle.bind(this)}>Ok <Ink/></button>
                        {this.state.correct && this.state.answered &&
                        <div className="riddle-success">Congratulations!</div>}
                        {!this.state.correct && this.state.answered &&
                        <div className="riddle-failed">Nope! That's not it</div>}
                    </div>
                </div>}

            </div>
        );
    }
}

export default Error;
